(suspenseful music)
I mean it.
I'm going.
No, you're not.
Because, as I've
already explained,
if a veil has been cast,
then there is a
strong likelihood
that he's still alive,
and he's there at
Satozakura High School.
I'll be back soon.
I'm ordering you to
wait there for me, Itadori.
It was probably pointless
to even ask him that.
As you heard, I need to go,
so I'll leave this to you, Ino.
What?
Why, is that a problem?
Well, um, it's just, um,
there's a lot of 'em,
and I think they're all humans.
I was thinking of
recommending you for promotion
to grade one sorcerer.
(Ino grunts)
All right, let's get this
done, baby! Ha ha!
(suspenseful music continues)
[Itadori] Please
step aside Ijichi.
Don't forget that our
job is to help others.
And though you're a student,
that includes even you, Itadori.
I'm not about to make
any more mistakes.
You mustn't go there, Itadori.
I'm sorry, Ijichi.
(suspenseful music continues)
What are you
doing? Stop, Junpei!
(lightning crashes)
Jujutsu sorcerer, back off.
(Opening Theme Music)
(man singing in Japanese)
(suspenseful music)
(Junpei panting)
(Itadori grunts)
[Junpei] Moon Dregs!
[Itadori] A jellyfish shikigami?
Blunt attacks won't even
touch him when he's inside that!
I'll say it one more time.
Stay out of this,
jujutsu sorcerer.
It's none of your business.
You don't tell me
what my business is!
What's the point, really,
of saving indiscriminately?
(Junpei grunts)
Don't overestimate
the value of a life!
(tentacles whipping)
(Itadori groans)
People always pretend
their emotions are everything,
but the heart is just the
metabolism of the soul.
It's all a delusion.
Don't restrict me with rules
that are based on a delusion.
What gives anyone the right
to stop someone
from taking a life?
Nothing does.
Now, just go sleep over there.
There's something I
have to go back and do.
(Junpei groans)
Your cursed technique is poison.
You produce poison
from cursed energy,
and then your
shikigami secretes it.
Soon you will learn
how to control their
size and their strength,
and that of the poison.
A normal jujutsu sorcerer
would need some time to grasp it,
but I'll teach you the sensation
so you'll be able
to fight right away.
Junpei, you have talent.
[Itadori] Who were you
trying to convince here?
(Itadori grunts)
(blows thudding)
(Itadori yells)
(Junpei groans)
[Junpei] Why, why doesn't
Moon Dregs' poison work on him?
-(shikigami thudding)
-(Junpei groaning)
Why are you getting
in my way? Why?
Why?
(blood splattering)
(Junpei grunting)
He's in the air,
so he can't dodge,
and now I have a chance to
crush him just before he lands.
(Itadori grunting)
(Itadori yells)
(Junpei groans)
Junpei, I really
can't understand
a single thing you're saying.
String together
whatever logic you want.
With shikigami, strike
the sorcerer directly.
But all you're doing is
trying to convince yourself
you're on the
right side of this.
-(punch booming)
-(glass shattering)
Even though I don't
know why you're doing this,
I'll assume you have
a good reason for it.
But whatever it is,
(melancholy music)
is it really worth throwing
away the life that you have?
(Junpei sobbing)
The human heart
is just a delusion?
Could you really say
that in front of her?
[Junpei] People
don't have hearts.
-You're still just
trying- -They don't!
Otherwise...
And that could only mean
that people cursed me and
my mom with those hearts.
That would just be too much.
Then I, I wouldn't even know
what is right and
what's wrong anymore.
(tentacles whipping)
(flesh squelching)
(melancholy music)
(Itadori groans)
Why didn't you dodge it?
I'm sorry.
I said a lot of arrogant stuff
without really
understanding anything.
So, tell me what happened
to you, and I swear to you,
if you do, then I won't
curse you anymore.
Please.
(melancholy music continues)
No way.
Your mom.
Junpei, join Jujutsu Tech.
You'd like it.
There are lots of
crazy strong teachers,
and good, reliable
friends there.
If we all work together,
I guarantee you,
we can find whoever it
was that cursed your mom.
Then you can make them
pay for what they did.
Let's fight together!
Huh?
(Mahito chuckles)
Who are you?
Who the hell's this?
Is it a person?
It's nice to meet you.
[Itadori] No, this feels like...
Vessel of Sukuna.
Mahito, no! Don't do it!
-(impact thudding)
-(Itadori groaning)
What am I, an idiot?
A human-shaped cursed
spirit with a patchwork face?
This is exactly what Nanami
told me would happen!
Junpei, get out!
I don't care what your
relationship is with him.
Right now, just get
your ass outta here. Run!
Itadori, calm down.
Mahito's not a bad person.
Huh?
(mysterious voices singing)
Bad person.
(brooding music)
You know, Junpei, you
are a pretty smart kid.
But sometimes, thinking
too much can lead
to even more foolish
decisions than impulsiveness.
You're a classic case of that.
I'd even say that you can
actually be almost as foolish
as those people you
call fools yourself.
And that's why you'll die.
Idle Transfiguration.
(Junpei groaning)
(dramatic music)
Now,
time for round two.
(Junpei growls)
Junpei.
-(punch thwacking)
-(Itadori groans)
Junpei!
Get ahold of yourself!
I can heal you!
(punches thudding)
Sukuna.
Sukuna!
What now?
(Mahito giggles)
I'll do anything.
I'll let you do whatever
you wanna do to me,
and all agree to any twisted
thing you come up with
if you heal Junpei,
like you did when
you restored my heart.
I refuse to. (laughs)
Oh.
[Itadori] Damn you!
(Sukuna laughs)
Excellent. He's completely
forgotten about that pact.
How very amusing.
You're offering your pride,
your future, and
your everything,
all just to grovel and beg
me for my help. (laughs)
By yourself, you
can't save anyone.
[Mahito] Is Sukuna
refusing the kid's pact?
The shape of one's
soul isn't something
that reverse-cursed
techniques could deal with, so,
maybe healing
others is beyond him?
How pitiful.
You couldn't be any more
pathetic, you sorry little punk.
(Sukuna laughs)
[Mahito] Although,
what I'm really after
is what comes next,
so I guess this will
do just fine. (laughs)
(dramatic music continues)
(Sukuna laughs)
[Itadori] Oh, that's right.
At the end of the day,
both of these two are curses.
[Junpei] Yuuji.
Help
me.
(body thudding)
(dramatic music continues)
(Mahito laughs)
Oh, dead already?
I was kind of rough when I
changed his shape, I'll admit.
That's how it goes.
(punch booming)
That was an unusual
blow. Interesting.
But sorry to say,
that won't work,
so long as I maintain
the shape of my...
Oh!
What's going on?
He struck the shape of my
soul, as well as my body?
Oh, that's right.
Yuuji Itadori is a vessel.
His body constantly
houses another soul
in addition to his own.
So, naturally...
You are actually aware
of the outline of your soul?
[Itadori] The next words
that spilled from my lips
came from so deep within my gut
that it nearly made everything
I've ever said feel like a lie.
I will kill you!
(upbeat music)
Don't you mean you'll
exorcize me, jujutsu sorcerer?
(Mahito slurps)
Yuuji Itadori isn't
concerned with his own life.
But Getou forbade
me from forcing him
into an external
pact using a hostages.
So, if he has a foe he hates
so much, he longs to kill them,
but he still can't, he'll
probably turn to Sukuna.
If Junpei pay isn't enough
then I'll have to
transform every student,
one by one,
before his very eyes.
That would push Itadori,
while he's all full of
hatred and self-interest,
to negotiate and forge
a pact with Sukuna.
If that also
improves the chances
of Sukuna joining our side,
then all the better. (slurps)
(dramatic music)
Though, all of that presumes
that I really am
stronger than him.
So, why did he have to be
my natural enemy?
(Itadori growls)
(Itadori yells)
(Mahito giggles)
[Itadori] He keeps
changing his damn shape!
I'd better stop using combos
and start using throwing
techniques instead.
[Mahito] Now that I know
his attacks work on me,
changing my shape and giving him
a bigger target is a bad idea.
[Both] In that case.
[Itadori] Even if it takes 100
times, or even 1,000 times,
I'm just going to
keep on pounding him
until I pound them into a pulp!
[Mahito] I'll use a shape
more refined toward murder,
with more
inspiration for murder,
and manifest it!
-(dramatic music)
-(Mahito roars)
(explosion booming)
(Mahito laughs)
(Itadori groans)
There's no way your limbs
can keep on stretching forever.
(flesh squelching)
(Itadori groans)
(dramatic music continues)
(Itadori roars)
[Mahito] You know, most
people would've just let go.
Spreading my shape
too much causes it
to lose strength
and maneuverability.
(Itadori yells)
(punch booming)
(Mahito giggles)
-(Itadori grunts)
-(punches booming)
(flesh squelching)
(brooding music)
Ah, you can never
beat me, you know,
so swap out already.
(Itadori groans)
With Sukuna.
Idle Transfiguration.
You dare to actually
touch my soul?
Since both of us heartily
ridiculed that brat before,
I'll allow it this once.
There won't be a second time.
Don't forget your place.
Foolish puppet.
I'm not swapping out.
I already told you.
For what you did, I
will kill you now. (roars)
(headbutt booming)
(headbutts thudding)
(blood splattering)
(kick booming)
(Itadori yells)
Huh?
(blade clanking)
Ha.
Uh?
Nanami?
(Nanami sighs)
I'll lecture you later.
Just tell me the situation.
Two died. I failed to save them.
Why is he always
thinking of others first?
I want to hear about
your physical condition.
I'm fine, thanks. Though,
I am kinda full of holes.
That's not fine.
Also, in the school gym,
the students are
alive, but unconscious.
My, my, so you're alive
and well, Mr. Seven-to-Three.
Good to see both of us survived.
Shall we share a little hug
in celebration of our reunion?
(suspenseful music)
[Nanami] Itadori, why
is his nose bleeding?
Uh, I smashed his face in?
But when?
At the start of the fight.
And did his hands touch you?
Mm-hmm.
[Nanami] My attacks
aren't going to work on him.
Huh?
Wait, what? But why not?
I'll explain it later,
when I'm lecturing you.
It's either because, one,
his technique doesn't
work on Itadori,
or two, there's some
reason he won't kill Itadori.
Either way, it's good for us.
However, I'll try to keep
him from moving around.
Then, once we
both got an opening,
we'll shower him with blows.
We'll exorcize this
one here and now.
Yeah!
(Closing Theme Music)
-(whimsical music)
-(voices moaning)
(whimsical music)
(creatures moaning)
Oh, look.
Huh?
Ah!
-Huh?
-(yellow man speaks gibberish)
(object clicks)
[Everyone] Huh?
-(object clicking)
-(creatures grunting)
-(pirate pops)
-Oh!
(creatures yelling)
(pirate clattering)
(dramatic music)